So you can see equally spaced 5 points between 0 and 1.
Now the big conceptual shift, the single most important thing, numpy changes about how
you write code, you stop looping, you start describing operations, take a simple example,
you have an array which is a test scores and you want to double each one, in plain python
you would write a loop up and to a new list and you would have your answer eventually or
you could use a list comprehension as well, in numpy you can directly write scores into
2.
So let us take this course for example, so if I just here, if I do this and let me comment
out the rest of the things, so you can see all the elements inside the numpy array got
doubled, that is it, numpy applies the same multiplication to every element in optimized